[SPEAKER 2]: This call is now being recorded.
[SPEAKER 2]: Good afternoon, MGK Design.
[SPEAKER 1]: Hi, I'm looking to have plans drawn up for an addition in my house.
[SPEAKER 2]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER 2]: Let me have one of our architects return your call.
[SPEAKER 2]: May I have your name, please?
[SPEAKER 1]: My name is John.
[SPEAKER 2]: John, and your last name?
[SPEAKER 1]: My last name is Lowry.
[SPEAKER 2]: Would you spell that for me, please?
[SPEAKER 1]: Okay, and your telephone number?
[SPEAKER 1]: Area code 610-265-1714.
[SPEAKER 2]: That's 610-265-1714?
[SPEAKER 1]: Yes, ma'am.
[SPEAKER 2]: Is there a good time to reach you?
[SPEAKER 1]: That's my cell, so you can catch me any time on that.
[SPEAKER 2]: Okay, great.
[SPEAKER 2]: I'll have him return your call as soon as possible.
[SPEAKER 1]: Great.
[SPEAKER 1]: Thank you very much.