[SPEAKER 2]: Call is now being recorded.
[SPEAKER 2]: Good afternoon, Elkins Builders.
[SPEAKER 1]: Yeah, hi.
[SPEAKER 1]: I'm calling to speak to someone about building a house on a property I'm looking to purchase.
[SPEAKER 2]: Oh, okay, great.
[SPEAKER 2]: Let me get your name.
[SPEAKER 2]: What's your first name, please?
[SPEAKER 1]: Kenny.
[SPEAKER 2]: And your last name?
[SPEAKER 1]: Lindstrom.
[SPEAKER 1]: It's L-I-N-D-S-T-R-O-M.
[SPEAKER 1]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER 2]: And may I have your callback number?
[SPEAKER 1]: It's 610-4-0-0-0.
[SPEAKER 1]: That's 610-265-1715?
[SPEAKER 1]: Yes.
[SPEAKER 2]: And where is the property that you're looking for an estimate on?
[SPEAKER 1]: It's in Westchester.
[SPEAKER 1]: I haven't purchased the land yet.
[SPEAKER 1]: I'd like to see if I could get an estimate or have them take a look at it before I do.
[SPEAKER 2]: Okay, no problem.
[SPEAKER 2]: And is there a good time to reach you with this number, or is that an any time?
[SPEAKER 1]: That's my cell phone.
[SPEAKER 1]: If they could call me back today, that would be great.
[SPEAKER 2]: Okay, no problem.
[SPEAKER 2]: I'll pass your message along, and somebody should be getting back to you this afternoon.
[SPEAKER 1]: Great.
[SPEAKER 1]: Thank you so much.
[SPEAKER 2]: You're welcome, and thank you for calling Elkins Builders.