Call is now being recorded.
Good afternoon, Elkins Builders.
Yeah, hi.
I'm calling to speak to someone about building a house on a property I'm looking to purchase.
Oh, okay, great.
Let me get your name.
What's your first name, please?
Kenny.
And your last name?
Lindstrom.
It's L-I-N-D-S-T-R-O-M.
Thank you.
And may I have your callback number?
It's 610-4-0-0-0.
That's 610-265-1715?
Yes.
And where is the property that you're looking for an estimate on?
It's in Westchester.
I haven't purchased the land yet.
I'd like to see if I could get an estimate or have them take a look at it before I do.
Okay, no problem.
And is there a good time to reach you with this number, or is that an any time?
That's my cell phone.
If they could call me back today, that would be great.
Okay, no problem.
I'll pass your message along, and somebody should be getting back to you this afternoon.
Great.
Thank you so much.
You're welcome, and thank you for calling Elkins Builders.