[SPEAKER 0]: Please say hello to start.
[SPEAKER 1]: Hello.
[SPEAKER 0]: I didn't understand your response.
[SPEAKER 0]: Please say hello to start.
[SPEAKER 1]: Hello.
[SPEAKER 0]: I'm sorry, sir.
[SPEAKER 0]: I can't understand you.
[SPEAKER 0]: Could you please repeat your response?
[SPEAKER 1]: Hello.
[SPEAKER 0]: I'm still waiting for your response.
[SPEAKER 0]: Please say hello to start.
[SPEAKER 1]: Hello.
[SPEAKER 0]: Calling iRabbit International Help Desk for assistance.
[SPEAKER 2]: Hello, sir.
[SPEAKER 2]: Thank you for purchasing the iRabbit, your own personal digital animal.
[SPEAKER 2]: T H I O Is that an O, sir?
[SPEAKER 1]: Yes.
[SPEAKER 1]: O R One more R.
[SPEAKER 2]: Y That is not a letter, sir.
[SPEAKER 1]: It's the letter Y.
[SPEAKER 2]: Can I just call you Greg, sir?
[SPEAKER 1]: I'm Thierry.
[SPEAKER 1]: Thierry.
[SPEAKER 2]: Bien sûr, monsieur.
[SPEAKER 2]: How can I help you today, Mr. Greg?
[SPEAKER 1]: I tried to start my iRabbit.
[SPEAKER 1]: It doesn't work.
[SPEAKER 1]: I'm very tired and hungry.
[SPEAKER 2]: Sir, if you're hungry, I can call you back after lunch.
[SPEAKER 1]: No, wait.
[SPEAKER 1]: I shake the rabbit.
[SPEAKER 1]: It doesn't function.
[SPEAKER 2]: Sir, please do not shake your iRabbit.
[SPEAKER 2]: Press the tail to start.
[SPEAKER 1]: I tried.
[SPEAKER 1]: It never works.
[SPEAKER 1]: I hate the rabbit.
[SPEAKER 2]: Sir, your one-year limited guarantee doesn't cover chewing or biting the device.
[SPEAKER 1]: No, I hate the rabbit.
[SPEAKER 2]: Kitting can cause fire in your house, sir.
[SPEAKER 2]: I understand that you are a non-vegetarian, Mr. Greg.
[SPEAKER 2]: But I would personally advise you to not eat the equipment, sir.
[SPEAKER 1]: Can I talk to your chef, please?
[SPEAKER 2]: I'm calling from iRabbit International Help Desk.
[SPEAKER 2]: It's not a restaurant, sir.
[SPEAKER 1]: No restaurant.
[SPEAKER 1]: I would like to talk to your chief.
[SPEAKER 2]: We are based in a developed country here.
[SPEAKER 2]: We don't have any chiefs or tribes now.
[SPEAKER 1]: But I paid a lot of money.
[SPEAKER 1]: It is not cheap.
[SPEAKER 2]: Exactly, sir.
[SPEAKER 2]: It's a rabbit, not a sheep.
[SPEAKER 1]: I mean it is not cheap.
[SPEAKER 1]: It's not cheap.
[SPEAKER 2]: It does have an electronic chip inside.
[SPEAKER 1]: Please, focus on my problem.
[SPEAKER 2]: I don't quite understand you, sir.
[SPEAKER 1]: Please focus.
[SPEAKER 2]: I beg your pardon?
[SPEAKER 1]: Please focus on the rabbit.
[SPEAKER 2]: I'm sorry, sir.
[SPEAKER 2]: I can't accept that kind of language.
[SPEAKER 2]: Thank you for purchasing the iRabbit, your personal digital animal.
[SPEAKER 1]: Hello.
[SPEAKER 0]: Welcome, Greg.
[SPEAKER 1]: The name is Thierry.
[SPEAKER 0]: Nice to meet you, Thierry.
[SPEAKER 0]: What can I do for you, Thierry?