Hi, it's Pat.
Can I help you?
Well, not really.
OK.
Is this Brandy?
Did Stephanie just say there's somebody on the line that needs help?
No, is this Brandy?
Yeah.
Yeah, hi, it's Pat.
They asked me to talk with you on this.
Apparently you're not going to get your order from Wilson Art, does that make sense?
When you expected it?
Well, yeah, I think I paid $350 to get in here and now I'm stuck with that in the kitchen for another week.
Right.
There's not a whole bunch I can do.
I can certainly refund you the shipping charges, but it looks like it's not going to be delivered until Tuesday.
And everything at our end is just one of those things that happen.
Our invoice, everything says it was shipped three days, but apparently Wilson Art, somewhere out in the warehouse, they just shipped it ground.
You know what?
I don't need you to get on the line and give me another excuse.
I mean, I've already heard it all.
I'm just telling you reality, ma'am.
Oh, I know what reality is.
What you're saying is, sorry, we're not accountable for what we sell.
We'll take your $350, but when it messes up, reality is, it's nobody's fault.
No, it's the shipping department's fault.
I mean, we don't physically go out there and package each one ourselves.
We have departments.
Wait a second.
You know what?
And life happens.
I mean, it does happen.
You bet it happens.
But you know what?
You need to take accountability.
Did you advertise the product?
And did you collect the $350 to have it shipped?
Yes, you did.
You can refuse the order, ma'am.
If you'd like to, just refuse it.
That's about the only thing I can offer.
I mean, I definitely will not charge you for the freight on the order.
I would hope not.
Well, yeah, I just offered that.
So it's not a hope thing.
It's a fact.
And if that's, you know, that's the best I can offer on that.
You always have the option of refusing it.
I do apologize.
And, you know, I'm taking responsibility for it.
I mean, what else can I do?
Well, you just got done saying that it was somebody else's fault, and that's reality.
That's exactly what you said.
It's somebody else's fault, and that's reality.
Okay, if that's what you want to look at.
You know what?
If I owned a business and I messed up like this, I would not get on the phone and start placing blame elsewhere.
Okay.
I wouldn't.
Okay, what do you want me to do?
And that's exactly what's wrong with America.
That's right.
You didn't own it.
I didn't own what?
They just hand me these things.
It's your mistake.
Did you sell the product?
Absolutely.
Absolutely you did.
And are we trying to compensate you for it?
What?
Do you want the product?
I don't know.
It depends on what I have to go find this weekend.
Does that even make it better?
No, it doesn't.
I'm sure it doesn't.
It's just...
No, it doesn't.
I have three kids and no kitchen.
You think anything you have to offer me right now is going to make it better?
Fuck you!
Are you still there?