[SPEAKER 2]: Hi, it's Pat.
[SPEAKER 2]: Can I help you?
[SPEAKER 1]: Well, not really.
[SPEAKER 2]: OK.
[SPEAKER 2]: Is this Brandy?
[SPEAKER 1]: Did Stephanie just say there's somebody on the line that needs help?
[SPEAKER 2]: No, is this Brandy?
[SPEAKER 2]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER 2]: Yeah, hi, it's Pat.
[SPEAKER 2]: They asked me to talk with you on this.
[SPEAKER 2]: Apparently you're not going to get your order from Wilson Art, does that make sense?
[SPEAKER 2]: When you expected it?
[SPEAKER 1]: Well, yeah, I think I paid $350 to get in here and now I'm stuck with that in the kitchen for another week.
[SPEAKER 2]: Right.
[SPEAKER 2]: There's not a whole bunch I can do.
[SPEAKER 2]: I can certainly refund you the shipping charges, but it looks like it's not going to be delivered until Tuesday.
[SPEAKER 2]: And everything at our end is just one of those things that happen.
[SPEAKER 2]: Our invoice, everything says it was shipped three days, but apparently Wilson Art, somewhere out in the warehouse, they just shipped it ground.
[SPEAKER 2]: You know what?
[SPEAKER 1]: I don't need you to get on the line and give me another excuse.
[SPEAKER 2]: I mean, I've already heard it all.
[SPEAKER 2]: I'm just telling you reality, ma'am.
[SPEAKER 1]: Oh, I know what reality is.
[SPEAKER 1]: What you're saying is, sorry, we're not accountable for what we sell.
[SPEAKER 1]: We'll take your $350, but when it messes up, reality is, it's nobody's fault.
[SPEAKER 2]: No, it's the shipping department's fault.
[SPEAKER 2]: I mean, we don't physically go out there and package each one ourselves.
[SPEAKER 2]: We have departments.
[SPEAKER 1]: Wait a second.
[SPEAKER 2]: You know what?
[SPEAKER 2]: And life happens.
[SPEAKER 2]: I mean, it does happen.
[SPEAKER 1]: You bet it happens.
[SPEAKER 1]: But you know what?
[SPEAKER 1]: You need to take accountability.
[SPEAKER 1]: Did you advertise the product?
[SPEAKER 1]: And did you collect the $350 to have it shipped?
[SPEAKER 2]: Yes, you did.
[SPEAKER 2]: You can refuse the order, ma'am.
[SPEAKER 2]: If you'd like to, just refuse it.
[SPEAKER 2]: That's about the only thing I can offer.
[SPEAKER 2]: I mean, I definitely will not charge you for the freight on the order.
[SPEAKER 1]: I would hope not.
[SPEAKER 2]: Well, yeah, I just offered that.
[SPEAKER 2]: So it's not a hope thing.
[SPEAKER 2]: It's a fact.
[SPEAKER 2]: And if that's, you know, that's the best I can offer on that.
[SPEAKER 2]: You always have the option of refusing it.
[SPEAKER 2]: I do apologize.
[SPEAKER 2]: And, you know, I'm taking responsibility for it.
[SPEAKER 2]: I mean, what else can I do?
[SPEAKER 1]: Well, you just got done saying that it was somebody else's fault, and that's reality.
[SPEAKER 1]: That's exactly what you said.
[SPEAKER 1]: It's somebody else's fault, and that's reality.
[SPEAKER 2]: Okay, if that's what you want to look at.
[SPEAKER 2]: You know what?
[SPEAKER 1]: If I owned a business and I messed up like this, I would not get on the phone and start placing blame elsewhere.
[SPEAKER 2]: Okay.
[SPEAKER 1]: I wouldn't.
[SPEAKER 2]: Okay, what do you want me to do?
[SPEAKER 1]: And that's exactly what's wrong with America.
[SPEAKER 2]: That's right.
[SPEAKER 1]: You didn't own it.
[SPEAKER 2]: I didn't own what?
[SPEAKER 2]: They just hand me these things.
[SPEAKER 1]: It's your mistake.
[SPEAKER 1]: Did you sell the product?
[SPEAKER 2]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER 1]: Absolutely you did.
[SPEAKER 2]: And are we trying to compensate you for it?
[SPEAKER 1]: What?
[SPEAKER 2]: Do you want the product?
[SPEAKER 2]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER 1]: It depends on what I have to go find this weekend.
[SPEAKER 1]: Does that even make it better?
[SPEAKER 1]: No, it doesn't.
[SPEAKER 2]: I'm sure it doesn't.
[SPEAKER 1]: It's just...
[SPEAKER 1]: No, it doesn't.
[SPEAKER 1]: I have three kids and no kitchen.
[SPEAKER 1]: You think anything you have to offer me right now is going to make it better?
[SPEAKER 2]: Fuck you!
[SPEAKER 1]: Fuck you!
[SPEAKER 2]: Are you still there?