Hello.
Hi, good afternoon.
Emma speaking with Tony Malfoman.
Yes.
Oh, hi there.
By the way, my name is Nelly and I'm calling from Medicare Online.
And by the way, ma'am, I'm calling you because there's been some recent changes about Medicare and we wanted to make sure that you are up to date on your policy.
And I believe, Miss Tony, you already have your Medicare Parts A and B, correct?
Mm-hmm.
All right.
That's great because of that you might eligible to lower your medication cost and we wanted to make sure also that you get your benefits including dental, vision, hearing, and over-the-counter for $0 monthly premium or no extra cost.
So are you receiving your benefits for no extra cost or additional cost at all?
No, no cost.
Is it for $0 copay also?
I don't know.
Okay.
Just to make sure, Tony, that you are receiving all of your upgraded benefits, I've got a licensed Medicare specialist on the other line to go over those amazing benefits and coverage for you, okay?
So just give us even five minutes of your time, all right?
Okay.
So, but before I'll connect the call, may I ask for the date of birth?
6-24-52.
Okay, 1952.
All right.
So how about your Medicare insurance plan?
So is it from Umana, Blue Cross Blue Shield, AARP, TRICARE?
What plan do you have right now?
I think it's AARP.
Okay, so you have AARP.
All right, so I'll connect the call now, Tony.
Just don't hang up the phone, okay?
Okay.
All right, thank you.
You have a wonderful day today.
You too.
Thank you.
Okay.
Hold on for a second.