Hello?
Hello, can you hear me good?
Yes, hello.
Oh, hi.
Good day, this is Mike Anderson from HP calling regarding a service event here.
And we are in the process of coordinating the V-Para for unit.
So our team has already began working to schedule this work order until today at 5 p.m.
Are you aware of this?
Yes, yes.
They had to find a technician because the original technician had to go home, I guess, for a family emergency.
Yes, that's fine by me.
I will be here.
1122 Ashbury Drive, Decataw, GA 30030.
That is correct.
And the technician, I'm assuming a new one has been assigned and they're going to pick up the battery at the other location?
Yes.
Perfect.
I will be here.
Thank you so much for your time, Dennis.
If there's any issue regarding to this work order, please don't hesitate to call us back at my direct phone number 985-365-0400 extension 848.
848.
That sounds great.
I've got it.
Thank you very much.
Thank you so much.
Bye for now.
Bye-bye.