[SPEAKER 1]: Hello?
[SPEAKER 2]: Hello, can you hear me good?
[SPEAKER 1]: Yes, hello.
[SPEAKER 2]: Oh, hi.
[SPEAKER 2]: Good day, this is Mike Anderson from HP calling regarding a service event here.
[SPEAKER 2]: And we are in the process of coordinating the V-Para for unit.
[SPEAKER 2]: So our team has already began working to schedule this work order until today at 5 p.m.
[SPEAKER 2]: Are you aware of this?
[SPEAKER 1]: Yes, yes.
[SPEAKER 1]: They had to find a technician because the original technician had to go home, I guess, for a family emergency.
[SPEAKER 2]: Yes, that's fine by me.
[SPEAKER 1]: I will be here.
[SPEAKER 2]: 1122 Ashbury Drive, Decataw, GA 30030.
[SPEAKER 1]: That is correct.
[SPEAKER 1]: And the technician, I'm assuming a new one has been assigned and they're going to pick up the battery at the other location?
[SPEAKER 2]: Yes.
[SPEAKER 1]: Perfect.
[SPEAKER 1]: I will be here.
[SPEAKER 2]: Thank you so much for your time, Dennis.
[SPEAKER 2]: If there's any issue regarding to this work order, please don't hesitate to call us back at my direct phone number 985-365-0400 extension 848.
[SPEAKER 1]: 848.
[SPEAKER 1]: That sounds great.
[SPEAKER 1]: I've got it.
[SPEAKER 1]: Thank you very much.
[SPEAKER 2]: Thank you so much.
[SPEAKER 2]: Bye for now.
[SPEAKER 1]: Bye-bye.