[SPEAKER 1]: Hello, this is Amos.
[SPEAKER 2]: Yeah, hi, good day.
[SPEAKER 2]: This is Amy from AHP.
[SPEAKER 2]: So I just want to confirm the appointment for the ticket number W-O-0-1-6-6-7-6-8-7-6.
[SPEAKER 2]: This one's for the system board and hard drive, also for RAM replacement.
[SPEAKER 1]: OK.
[SPEAKER 2]: Yes, I just want to confirm, yes, if this one, yes, appointment for today or tomorrow.
[SPEAKER 1]: This is the first call I've received about an appointment for this, so I don't know.
[SPEAKER 2]: Oh, I see.
[SPEAKER 2]: Yes, because we already assigned a technician to do this appointment.
[SPEAKER 1]: OK.
[SPEAKER 2]: But, yes, he just wants to clear if you're available tomorrow at 10 a.m.
[SPEAKER 1]: Yes, yes, I am.
[SPEAKER 2]: Oh, OK, great.
[SPEAKER 2]: So thank you so much for letting us know, Amos.
[SPEAKER 2]: So we'll just call you back tomorrow to have some updates about this one.
[SPEAKER 1]: OK.
[SPEAKER 2]: All right, bye.
[SPEAKER 1]: Bye.