[SPEAKER 1]: Call is now being recorded.
[SPEAKER 2]: ABC Plumbing and Heating, this is Betty.
[SPEAKER 1]: Hi Betty, I'm having a problem with my sewer drain.
[SPEAKER 2]: Oh, I'm so sorry to hear that, sir.
[SPEAKER 2]: Would you like me to get a hold of the plumber for you?
[SPEAKER 1]: Do you know how much it's going to cost?
[SPEAKER 2]: Unfortunately, I wouldn't be able to quote prices, but I can get a hold of someone who would be able to give you a better idea.
[SPEAKER 1]: I'm getting a backup throughout the entire house.
[SPEAKER 2]: Are you a client of ABC?
[SPEAKER 1]: I did use them before to put in my garbage disposal, but nothing major like this.
[SPEAKER 2]: Okay, let me get your name and number and I can patch you right through to the plumber.
[SPEAKER 2]: Your name, sir?
[SPEAKER 1]: Mike Barry.
[SPEAKER 2]: Would you spell your last name for me, please?
[SPEAKER 1]: That's B-A-R-R-Y.
[SPEAKER 2]: Okay, and your callback number?
[SPEAKER 1]: 610-265-1714.
[SPEAKER 2]: Okay, that's 610-265-1714.
[SPEAKER 1]: Yes, will he call me right back?
[SPEAKER 2]: Actually, Mr. Barry, I'm going to call him right now and patch you directly through to the plumber.
[SPEAKER 2]: Would you stay on the line for a moment?
[SPEAKER 1]: Oh, sure.
[SPEAKER 1]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER 1]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER 2]: Okay, hold on.