Call is now being recorded.
ABC Plumbing and Heating, this is Betty.
Hi Betty, I'm having a problem with my sewer drain.
Oh, I'm so sorry to hear that, sir.
Would you like me to get a hold of the plumber for you?
Do you know how much it's going to cost?
Unfortunately, I wouldn't be able to quote prices, but I can get a hold of someone who would be able to give you a better idea.
I'm getting a backup throughout the entire house.
Are you a client of ABC?
I did use them before to put in my garbage disposal, but nothing major like this.
Okay, let me get your name and number and I can patch you right through to the plumber.
Your name, sir?
Mike Barry.
Would you spell your last name for me, please?
That's B-A-R-R-Y.
Okay, and your callback number?
610-265-1714.
Okay, that's 610-265-1714.
Yes, will he call me right back?
Actually, Mr. Barry, I'm going to call him right now and patch you directly through to the plumber.
Would you stay on the line for a moment?
Oh, sure.
Awesome.
Thank you.
Okay, hold on.