[SPEAKER 1]: Hey, G-Trans, this is Jennifer.
[SPEAKER 2]: Yes, hi Jennifer, good afternoon ma'am.
[SPEAKER 2]: This is Gabby from TransPlace AP team and I'm calling to request for a copy of carrier invoice, bill of lading, and proof of delivery.
[SPEAKER 2]: Can you assist me with this?
[SPEAKER 1]: Sure.
[SPEAKER 1]: Do you have my invoice number or?
[SPEAKER 2]: All right, let me check here.
[SPEAKER 2]: Well, actually I have a total of four shipments.
[SPEAKER 2]: So if you want I can go ahead and send it to your email instead for you to check.
[SPEAKER 1]: Sure, that'd be great.
[SPEAKER 2]: Yeah, what's your email?
[SPEAKER 1]: It's accounting at agtransportationinc.com All right, again it's accounting at ag.
[SPEAKER 1]: ag, Apple George, transportationinc.com.
[SPEAKER 2]: I'm sorry, again it's transportationinc.com, right?
[SPEAKER 1]: Yeah, you got it.
[SPEAKER 2]: Okay, all right.
[SPEAKER 2]: Okay, so again it's accounting at agtransportationinc.com, right?
[SPEAKER 1]: You got it, yep.
[SPEAKER 2]: Okay, all right.
[SPEAKER 1]: Okay.
[SPEAKER 2]: Yeah, so I'll be sending this shipping documents right after this call.
[SPEAKER 2]: Thank you so much.
[SPEAKER 1]: Okay, thank you.