Hey, G-Trans, this is Jennifer.
Yes, hi Jennifer, good afternoon ma'am.
This is Gabby from TransPlace AP team and I'm calling to request for a copy of carrier invoice, bill of lading, and proof of delivery.
Can you assist me with this?
Sure.
Do you have my invoice number or?
All right, let me check here.
Well, actually I have a total of four shipments.
So if you want I can go ahead and send it to your email instead for you to check.
Sure, that'd be great.
Yeah, what's your email?
It's accounting at agtransportationinc.com All right, again it's accounting at ag.
ag, Apple George, transportationinc.com.
I'm sorry, again it's transportationinc.com, right?
Yeah, you got it.
Okay, all right.
Okay, so again it's accounting at agtransportationinc.com, right?
You got it, yep.
Okay, all right.
Okay.
Yeah, so I'll be sending this shipping documents right after this call.
Thank you so much.
Okay, thank you.