Call is now being recorded.
Good evening, Kingswood Apartments.
This is Alex.
How may I help you?
Hey, yeah, I'm in apartment 104 on the first floor.
I'm calling to complain about my neighbors.
Okay, what seems to be the problem, sir?
It's very late.
I just got my newborn baby to sleep, and they're being loud again.
I brought this to their attention several times, but they never, you know, never stops.
Okay, I'm very sorry about that.
I'm sorry about that.
Just let me take down your contact information, and I'll contact the landlord right away to get this all straightened out.
Okay, my name is Jeff Matthews.
Okay, Mr. Matthews, can you spell that for me?
First name is Jeff, J-E-F-F.
Last name is Matthews, M-A-T-T-H-E-W-S.
Okay, Mr. Matthews, can I have the best number you can be reached at, and also your apartment number again?
Sure, it's 610-265-1714, and I'm in apartment 104 on the first floor.
Okay, I have 610-265-1714 and apartment 104.
Yes.
All right, Mr. Matthews, I'm going to pass this information onto the landlord right away, and he'll be contacting you shortly.
Is there anything else I can help you with today?
No, that's all.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Have a great night.
You too.