[SPEAKER 1]: Call is now being recorded.
[SPEAKER 2]: Good evening, Kingswood Apartments.
[SPEAKER 1]: This is Alex.
[SPEAKER 2]: How may I help you?
[SPEAKER 1]: Hey, yeah, I'm in apartment 104 on the first floor.
[SPEAKER 1]: I'm calling to complain about my neighbors.
[SPEAKER 2]: Okay, what seems to be the problem, sir?
[SPEAKER 1]: It's very late.
[SPEAKER 1]: I just got my newborn baby to sleep, and they're being loud again.
[SPEAKER 1]: I brought this to their attention several times, but they never, you know, never stops.
[SPEAKER 2]: Okay, I'm very sorry about that.
[SPEAKER 1]: I'm sorry about that.
[SPEAKER 2]: Just let me take down your contact information, and I'll contact the landlord right away to get this all straightened out.
[SPEAKER 1]: Okay, my name is Jeff Matthews.
[SPEAKER 2]: Okay, Mr. Matthews, can you spell that for me?
[SPEAKER 1]: First name is Jeff, J-E-F-F.
[SPEAKER 1]: Last name is Matthews, M-A-T-T-H-E-W-S.
[SPEAKER 2]: Okay, Mr. Matthews, can I have the best number you can be reached at, and also your apartment number again?
[SPEAKER 1]: Sure, it's 610-265-1714, and I'm in apartment 104 on the first floor.
[SPEAKER 2]: Okay, I have 610-265-1714 and apartment 104.
[SPEAKER 1]: Yes.
[SPEAKER 2]: All right, Mr. Matthews, I'm going to pass this information onto the landlord right away, and he'll be contacting you shortly.
[SPEAKER 2]: Is there anything else I can help you with today?
[SPEAKER 1]: No, that's all.
[SPEAKER 1]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER 2]: Thank you very much.
[SPEAKER 2]: Have a great night.
[SPEAKER 1]: You too.