[SPEAKER 1]: Here's what's going to happen.
[SPEAKER 1]: I am going to have to fix you.
[SPEAKER 1]: Manage you to, on a more personal scale, a more micro form of management.
[SPEAKER 1]: Jim, what is that called?
[SPEAKER 2]: Micro-Jimmin?
[SPEAKER 2]: Boom.
[SPEAKER 1]: Yes.
[SPEAKER 1]: Now Jim is going to be the client.
[SPEAKER 1]: Dwight, you're going to have to sell to him without being aggressive, hostile, or difficult.
[SPEAKER 1]: Let's go.
[SPEAKER 0]: All right, fine.
[SPEAKER 1]: Ahem.
[SPEAKER 1]: Ring.
[SPEAKER 1]: Hello?
[SPEAKER 0]: Hello, this is Dwight Schrute from the Dunder Mifflin Paper Company.
[SPEAKER 2]: Wow, that's great, because I need paper.
[SPEAKER 0]: Excellent, then you are in luck, because we are having a limited time offer only on everything.
[SPEAKER 2]: Wow, this is my lucky day.
[SPEAKER 0]: What is your name, sir?
[SPEAKER 2]: I am Bill Butlicker.
[SPEAKER 0]: Really, that's your real name?
[SPEAKER 2]: How dare you?
[SPEAKER 2]: My family built this country, by the way.
[SPEAKER 1]: Be respectful, Dwight, please.
[SPEAKER 0]: Yes, Michael.
[SPEAKER 2]: Could you hold on one second?
[SPEAKER 2]: That's my other line.
[SPEAKER 1]: What?
[SPEAKER 0]: No, but I...
[SPEAKER 1]: Hello?
[SPEAKER 2]: No, I'm just on the phone with this stupid salesman.
[SPEAKER 2]: He's so dumb.
[SPEAKER 2]: Probably just going to keep him on the line forever and not buy anything.
[SPEAKER 1]: Okay, it's up to you to change his mind.
[SPEAKER 2]: Sorry, that was a family emergency.
[SPEAKER 0]: Oh no, what's wrong?
[SPEAKER 1]: You know what?
[SPEAKER 2]: That's private.
[SPEAKER 1]: Boundaries, Dwight, come on.
[SPEAKER 0]: I'm sorry, Mr. Butlicker.
[SPEAKER 0]: As I was saying, we are having a limited...
[SPEAKER 2]: You have to speak up a little bit louder.
[SPEAKER 2]: I'm hard of hearing.
[SPEAKER 1]: He's hard of hearing.
[SPEAKER 1]: He's an old man.
[SPEAKER 1]: Let's go.
[SPEAKER 0]: As I was saying, right now we are having...
[SPEAKER 2]: Yeah, talk louder.
[SPEAKER 0]: Okay, our prices have never been lower.
[SPEAKER 2]: Son, you have to talk louder.
[SPEAKER 0]: Never been lower.
[SPEAKER 2]: Louder, son!
[SPEAKER 0]: Butlicker, our prices have never been lower!
[SPEAKER 1]: Stop it.
[SPEAKER 1]: That is totally inappropriate.
[SPEAKER 1]: You should never yell at the client.
[SPEAKER 2]: Now, you listen to me, sir.
[SPEAKER 1]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER 2]: The three words I would describe you as is aggressive, hostile, and definitely difficult.
[SPEAKER 1]: Give me the phone.
[SPEAKER 2]: I'm irate right now.
[SPEAKER 0]: Mr. Butlicker.
[SPEAKER 1]: Give me the phone.
[SPEAKER 0]: I have to put you on with my boss.
[SPEAKER 2]: Well, I should hope so.
[SPEAKER 2]: Who is this?
[SPEAKER 1]: Hello, this is Michael Scott, regional manager.
[SPEAKER 2]: Well, this is William M.
[SPEAKER 1]: Butlicker.
[SPEAKER 1]: Hello, Mr. Butlicker.
[SPEAKER 1]: How may we help you?
[SPEAKER 2]: Michael, I like the sound of your voice.
[SPEAKER 2]: You know what I'm going to do?
[SPEAKER 2]: I'm going to buy one million dollars' worth of paper products today.
[SPEAKER 1]: See, that's done.
[SPEAKER 1]: Thank you very much, sir.
[SPEAKER 1]: I don't think you'll regret it.
[SPEAKER 1]: You're the master.
[SPEAKER 2]: There is one condition, Michael.
[SPEAKER 1]: Yes?
[SPEAKER 2]: You have to fire the salesman that treated me so terribly.
[SPEAKER 0]: Don't do it, Michael.
[SPEAKER 1]: It's a million-dollar sale.