Here's what's going to happen.
I am going to have to fix you.
Manage you to, on a more personal scale, a more micro form of management.
Jim, what is that called?
Micro-Jimmin?
Boom.
Yes.
Now Jim is going to be the client.
Dwight, you're going to have to sell to him without being aggressive, hostile, or difficult.
Let's go.
All right, fine.
Ahem.
Ring.
Hello?
Hello, this is Dwight Schrute from the Dunder Mifflin Paper Company.
Wow, that's great, because I need paper.
Excellent, then you are in luck, because we are having a limited time offer only on everything.
Wow, this is my lucky day.
What is your name, sir?
I am Bill Butlicker.
Really, that's your real name?
How dare you?
My family built this country, by the way.
Be respectful, Dwight, please.
Yes, Michael.
Could you hold on one second?
That's my other line.
What?
No, but I...
Hello?
No, I'm just on the phone with this stupid salesman.
He's so dumb.
Probably just going to keep him on the line forever and not buy anything.
Okay, it's up to you to change his mind.
Sorry, that was a family emergency.
Oh no, what's wrong?
You know what?
That's private.
Boundaries, Dwight, come on.
I'm sorry, Mr. Butlicker.
As I was saying, we are having a limited...
You have to speak up a little bit louder.
I'm hard of hearing.
He's hard of hearing.
He's an old man.
Let's go.
As I was saying, right now we are having...
Yeah, talk louder.
Okay, our prices have never been lower.
Son, you have to talk louder.
Never been lower.
Louder, son!
Butlicker, our prices have never been lower!
Stop it.
That is totally inappropriate.
You should never yell at the client.
Now, you listen to me, sir.
Here we go.
The three words I would describe you as is aggressive, hostile, and definitely difficult.
Give me the phone.
I'm irate right now.
Mr. Butlicker.
Give me the phone.
I have to put you on with my boss.
Well, I should hope so.
Who is this?
Hello, this is Michael Scott, regional manager.
Well, this is William M.
Butlicker.
Hello, Mr. Butlicker.
How may we help you?
Michael, I like the sound of your voice.
You know what I'm going to do?
I'm going to buy one million dollars' worth of paper products today.
See, that's done.
Thank you very much, sir.
I don't think you'll regret it.
You're the master.
There is one condition, Michael.
Yes?
You have to fire the salesman that treated me so terribly.
Don't do it, Michael.
It's a million-dollar sale.