[SPEAKER 1]: Hello Eloise, speaking.
[SPEAKER 2]: Hi Eloise, this is Sophia.
[SPEAKER 2]: Good day.
[SPEAKER 2]: I'm phoning from the realestateleadgeneration.com.au.
[SPEAKER 2]: We just want to quickly let you know our custom lead generation packages are now live.
[SPEAKER 2]: We're getting real estate agent leads as we speak.
[SPEAKER 2]: I know you're busy Eloise, but I hope your team is already set up with a stable stream of incoming leads, property appraisals, property management, and general inquiries.
[SPEAKER 2]: That's fine.
[SPEAKER 2]: We'll leave you to it.
[SPEAKER 2]: But we've been working with real estate agencies for over 10 years and there's always a common theme.
[SPEAKER 2]: Where is your next lead going to come from?
[SPEAKER 2]: So my call today is just to book a time with one of our real estate lead specialists who are based in both Sydney and Melbourne.
[SPEAKER 2]: They'll quickly introduce the package to you.
[SPEAKER 2]: Just run through a few of the finer details, Eloise.
[SPEAKER 2]: It'll only take 10 to 20 minutes to give you the background of the package.
[SPEAKER 2]: They'll let you ask any questions you may have.
[SPEAKER 2]: Are you free next week, Wednesday, during the morning or after lunch?
[SPEAKER 1]: No, I'm really sorry.
[SPEAKER 1]: I'll be running around at open.
[SPEAKER 2]: What about Friday next week?
[SPEAKER 2]: Or we can do April appointments as well.
[SPEAKER 1]: I don't actually understand.
[SPEAKER 1]: What is it?
[SPEAKER 2]: Custom lead generation package.
[SPEAKER 2]: This is your line of business, right?
[SPEAKER 2]: Real estate?
[SPEAKER 1]: Yes.
[SPEAKER 2]: So these are just custom lead generations.
[SPEAKER 2]: To be honest, I don't really have the information for the package.
[SPEAKER 2]: What I really do is just to connect you to our real estate lead specialist so that they could discuss the package with you.
[SPEAKER 2]: Any questions that you may have, they'd be able to answer it for you most definitely through the appointment.
[SPEAKER 2]: It'll just take like 10 to 20 minutes.
[SPEAKER 1]: I'm out at the moment.
[SPEAKER 1]: Are you able to send me an email and I can have a look at it and then confirm a time?
[SPEAKER 2]: I won't be able to.
[SPEAKER 2]: To be honest, we call out so I don't really have a means to email out.
[SPEAKER 2]: I could set you up for Friday next week and we still have from 10am to 12.30.
[SPEAKER 1]: No, thanks.
[SPEAKER 1]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER 2]: What about if I call you back next week and then perhaps we can get an appointment time for you next week?
[SPEAKER 1]: Okay, that sounds good.
[SPEAKER 2]: Alright, I'll call you back Monday?
[SPEAKER 2]: Alright, thank you.
[SPEAKER 2]: Thank you so much.
[SPEAKER 2]: Have a good day today.
[SPEAKER 2]: Enjoy your weekend.
[SPEAKER 2]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER 1]: Bye.