Hello, Anthony speaking.
Hi Anthony, this is Francis.
I'm calling from realestatelegeneration.com.au.
Hi, how are you?
I'm doing good.
Thanks for asking and thank you for taking my call.
I'm just getting in touch quickly today to let you know our custom lead generation packages are now live and getting real estate agents lead as we speak.
I know you're busy and if your team is set up with a stable stream of incoming leads for property appraisals, property management and general inquiries, that's okay.
I'll leave you to it.
To be honest, John, we've been working with real estate agencies for over 10 years and there's always a common theme.
Where's my next lead coming from?
My call today is to book a time with one of our real estate lead specialists who are based in both Sydney and Melbourne to introduce the package to you and run through a few of the finer details.
This will only take between 10 to 20 minutes to give you the background of the package and let you ask any questions you might have.
Is it next 23rd of March and the afternoon suits to you?
Would that be okay to call you?
Yes, to give me a call?
Yes, definitely.
Just because I'm running into a meeting in the next two minutes, I just have to get ready for that.
Someone can call me then.
Great.
Mind if I have your email?
Yes, it's Anthony, A-N-T-H-O-N-Y.
Okay.
At Home Property Agents.
Home Property Agents with an S at the end.
Uh-huh.
Dot com dot au.
So, Anthony at Home Property Agents dot com dot au, right?
That's it.
So, yeah, my specialist will give you a quick call to confirm the time and date beforehand and they will quickly introduce themselves and send you information via email and you can have a look at also our website.
It's realestateleadgeneration.com.au and they're going to call you March 23rd, Tuesday around 3 PM.
Okay?
Sounds good.
Thank you so much.
Okay.
Bye-bye.
Have a wonderful day.
Don't forget to check your email, Anthony.
Will do.
Thank you.