[SPEAKER 1]: Call is now being recorded.
[SPEAKER 1]: Good afternoon, Mountain Security Services.
[SPEAKER 2]: Hi, I'm calling to give an estimate on having a system installed in my house.
[SPEAKER 1]: Let me get your information and I'll have a security specialist give you a call and discuss your needs.
[SPEAKER 1]: First, could I have your name, sir?
[SPEAKER 2]: It's Brad Fagan.
[SPEAKER 1]: Could you spell the last name, please?
[SPEAKER 2]: F-A-G-E-N.
[SPEAKER 1]: And a number where you can be reached, Brad.
[SPEAKER 2]: 610-265-1715.
[SPEAKER 1]: And could I get the address of where you would like the security system installed?
[SPEAKER 2]: Sure, it's 800 North Henderson Road in King of Prussia.
[SPEAKER 1]: That's Henderson, H-E-N-D-E-R-S-O-N?
[SPEAKER 2]: Yes.
[SPEAKER 1]: And would you spell the name of the city, please?
[SPEAKER 2]: Sure, it's King of Prussia.
[SPEAKER 2]: P-R-U-S-S-I-A.
[SPEAKER 1]: And your zip code?
[SPEAKER 2]: 19406.
[SPEAKER 1]: Thank you, Mr. Fagan.
[SPEAKER 1]: A security specialist will be calling you momentarily.
[SPEAKER 1]: Is there anything else that I can do for you today?
[SPEAKER 2]: No, I appreciate your help.
[SPEAKER 2]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER 1]: Okay, thank you.
[SPEAKER 1]: Have a great day.
[SPEAKER 2]: You too, bye-bye.