Call is now being recorded.
Good afternoon, Mountain Security Services.
Hi, I'm calling to give an estimate on having a system installed in my house.
Let me get your information and I'll have a security specialist give you a call and discuss your needs.
First, could I have your name, sir?
It's Brad Fagan.
Could you spell the last name, please?
F-A-G-E-N.
And a number where you can be reached, Brad.
610-265-1715.
And could I get the address of where you would like the security system installed?
Sure, it's 800 North Henderson Road in King of Prussia.
That's Henderson, H-E-N-D-E-R-S-O-N?
Yes.
And would you spell the name of the city, please?
Sure, it's King of Prussia.
P-R-U-S-S-I-A.
And your zip code?
19406.
Thank you, Mr. Fagan.
A security specialist will be calling you momentarily.
Is there anything else that I can do for you today?
No, I appreciate your help.
Thank you.
Okay, thank you.
Have a great day.
You too, bye-bye.