[SPEAKER 2]: Hello, is this Jess?
[SPEAKER 1]: Yes, it's yours.
[SPEAKER 2]: Hi, this is Stella from Barrister.
[SPEAKER 2]: I'm calling because I have an open ticket for you in 100 East Tyler Street, Tampa, Florida.
[SPEAKER 2]: The zip code is 33606.
[SPEAKER 2]: And this is for Santa Air Direct Unit to complete installation.
[SPEAKER 2]: Are you available for this work order?
[SPEAKER 1]: I'm not in Tampa right now.
[SPEAKER 1]: I live in Orlando.
[SPEAKER 1]: You said it's an open ticket?
[SPEAKER 1]: Like it's on my log or something?
[SPEAKER 2]: This is a work order for you.
[SPEAKER 2]: The work request number is 4744244.
[SPEAKER 1]: But what I was saying is, is this like a new order or no?
[SPEAKER 1]: Is this a new ticket?
[SPEAKER 2]: Sorry?
[SPEAKER 2]: Yes, sir.
[SPEAKER 1]: Oh, okay, that's what I'm saying.
[SPEAKER 1]: I don't live in Tampa.
[SPEAKER 1]: It's kind of out of my way that I wouldn't be able to cover that this week or anything.
[SPEAKER 2]: Okay, how about this?
[SPEAKER 2]: Another ticket that I have here in 5281 Airport Service Road, Tampa, Florida.
[SPEAKER 2]: The zip code is 33607.
[SPEAKER 2]: And this is for miscellaneous services?
[SPEAKER 1]: Yeah, like right now, like this week, I live in Orlando, so I'm not anywhere near Tampa.
[SPEAKER 1]: I'm like two and a half hours away from Tampa, so I couldn't cover anything over there this week.
[SPEAKER 2]: All right, okay.
[SPEAKER 2]: So thank you so much for taking this call.
[SPEAKER 2]: Have a great day.
[SPEAKER 2]: Hey, you too.
[SPEAKER 1]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER 2]: All right.