Hello.
Good morning.
I'm a...
Hello.
Who's calling, please?
Hello, good morning.
My name is Alexis, and I'm calling you right now from Barrister Global Services.
And the purpose of my call, Mr. David, is to tell you that we are looking for quality field technicians in Colorado Springs.
So I just wanted to ask if you have a moment to answer a few questions.
Sure.
Okay.
Well, just to let you know a little bit about Barrister Global Services, Mr. David, what we are is a multi-vendor company that provides help desk, networking, staffing, and technician services.
So we have clients such as HP.
What they do is they open cases for their customers, and then they send those cases to us, Barrister, so we can supply them a quality technician to do the job.
And I read here that you are a field technician.
Is that correct?
Yes.
Okay, perfect.
Well, so what we're offering you here, Mr. David, is an opportunity to earn or supplement your income with service work that you can accept or decline on a work order by work order basis, meaning you can work on them based on your own schedule and at your own pace.
Are you interested?
I'm not sure what kind of work.
I mean, I understand the work.
I get a lot of work already.
I just don't know if it's, you know, what you guys pay, all that kind of stuff.
Oh, okay.
Because I'm not going to work for a lot of money, you know.
Well, let me tell you when on, you know, on how it's going to work.
So, here, Mr. David, once you sign up as one of our technicians, you will be provided with a technician portal.
It's an application that you can install on your phone.
It's installable both on Android and iOS.
And on that application, we will be providing you all the available customers and cases on your area.
So in this case, you can pick and choose which customers and cases you would like to work for.
And also, it is not mandatory for you to accept all these cases.
You can work on them based on your own schedule.
And so, your payment is very easy because once you close out the service order or the work order, the payment will reflect right away.
And also, our minimum pay that we have right now is $50.
That's per hour.
So it really depends on which service that you provide.
So it can go higher than that, depending on your skill set.
I see.
Okay.
So are you interested?
Possibly.
Do I have to pay anything to join up with this program or what?
You do not have to pay for anything, Mr. David.
Well, if you're interested, I just need to ask you a few questions.
Just wanted to know if you have at least one year of experience in the field.
Yes, I have many years of experience.
Oh, okay.
That's perfect.
And are you a citizen of the U.S.
or by law be permitted to work?
Yes.
Okay, perfect.
And are you able to provide a current government secured ID or a driver's license?
Yes.
Okay, perfect.
So do you have time right now, Mr. David, to set up your profile so I can walk you through the following steps?
Or would you like me to send it to you through email?
Send me something through email so I can look at it because I got to go.
I'm heading out to go to work and stuff.
That's okay.
So, Mr. David, I have your email address here.
Just verify if it's the correct one.
I have home underscore user at Comcast.net.
Is that correct?
No, that's an old one.
No.
My new email, I've had years, is the.omnizoa at gmail.
T-H-E dot O-M-N-I-Z-O-A at gmail.com.
Okay, got that, Mr. David.
I'll be sending an email under my name, which is Alexis Stewart.
And yeah, is it okay with you if I give you a call back maybe after working hours just to check if you were able to receive my email?
Sure.
Okay.
All right.
Thank you so much, Mr. David.
This is Alexis again.
Have a great day on your work and keep safe, okay?
You too.
Bye.
Okay, bye.