[SPEAKER 1]: Hello.
[SPEAKER 1]: Good morning.
[SPEAKER 1]: I'm a...
[SPEAKER 2]: Hello.
[SPEAKER 2]: Who's calling, please?
[SPEAKER 1]: Hello, good morning.
[SPEAKER 1]: My name is Alexis, and I'm calling you right now from Barrister Global Services.
[SPEAKER 1]: And the purpose of my call, Mr. David, is to tell you that we are looking for quality field technicians in Colorado Springs.
[SPEAKER 1]: So I just wanted to ask if you have a moment to answer a few questions.
[SPEAKER 2]: Sure.
[SPEAKER 1]: Okay.
[SPEAKER 1]: Well, just to let you know a little bit about Barrister Global Services, Mr. David, what we are is a multi-vendor company that provides help desk, networking, staffing, and technician services.
[SPEAKER 1]: So we have clients such as HP.
[SPEAKER 1]: What they do is they open cases for their customers, and then they send those cases to us, Barrister, so we can supply them a quality technician to do the job.
[SPEAKER 1]: And I read here that you are a field technician.
[SPEAKER 1]: Is that correct?
[SPEAKER 2]: Yes.
[SPEAKER 1]: Okay, perfect.
[SPEAKER 1]: Well, so what we're offering you here, Mr. David, is an opportunity to earn or supplement your income with service work that you can accept or decline on a work order by work order basis, meaning you can work on them based on your own schedule and at your own pace.
[SPEAKER 1]: Are you interested?
[SPEAKER 2]: I'm not sure what kind of work.
[SPEAKER 2]: I mean, I understand the work.
[SPEAKER 2]: I get a lot of work already.
[SPEAKER 2]: I just don't know if it's, you know, what you guys pay, all that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER 1]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER 2]: Because I'm not going to work for a lot of money, you know.
[SPEAKER 2]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER 1]: Well, let me tell you when on, you know, on how it's going to work.
[SPEAKER 1]: So, here, Mr. David, once you sign up as one of our technicians, you will be provided with a technician portal.
[SPEAKER 1]: It's an application that you can install on your phone.
[SPEAKER 1]: It's installable both on Android and iOS.
[SPEAKER 1]: And on that application, we will be providing you all the available customers and cases on your area.
[SPEAKER 1]: So in this case, you can pick and choose which customers and cases you would like to work for.
[SPEAKER 1]: And also, it is not mandatory for you to accept all these cases.
[SPEAKER 1]: You can work on them based on your own schedule.
[SPEAKER 1]: And so, your payment is very easy because once you close out the service order or the work order, the payment will reflect right away.
[SPEAKER 1]: And also, our minimum pay that we have right now is $50.
[SPEAKER 1]: That's per hour.
[SPEAKER 1]: So it really depends on which service that you provide.
[SPEAKER 1]: So it can go higher than that, depending on your skill set.
[SPEAKER 1]: I see.
[SPEAKER 2]: Okay.
[SPEAKER 1]: So are you interested?
[SPEAKER 2]: Possibly.
[SPEAKER 2]: Do I have to pay anything to join up with this program or what?
[SPEAKER 1]: You do not have to pay for anything, Mr. David.
[SPEAKER 1]: Well, if you're interested, I just need to ask you a few questions.
[SPEAKER 1]: Just wanted to know if you have at least one year of experience in the field.
[SPEAKER 2]: Yes, I have many years of experience.
[SPEAKER 1]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER 1]: That's perfect.
[SPEAKER 1]: And are you a citizen of the U.S.
[SPEAKER 1]: or by law be permitted to work?
[SPEAKER 1]: Yes.
[SPEAKER 1]: Okay, perfect.
[SPEAKER 1]: And are you able to provide a current government secured ID or a driver's license?
[SPEAKER 2]: Yes.
[SPEAKER 1]: Okay, perfect.
[SPEAKER 1]: So do you have time right now, Mr. David, to set up your profile so I can walk you through the following steps?
[SPEAKER 1]: Or would you like me to send it to you through email?
[SPEAKER 2]: Send me something through email so I can look at it because I got to go.
[SPEAKER 2]: I'm heading out to go to work and stuff.
[SPEAKER 2]: That's okay.
[SPEAKER 1]: So, Mr. David, I have your email address here.
[SPEAKER 1]: Just verify if it's the correct one.
[SPEAKER 1]: I have home underscore user at Comcast.net.
[SPEAKER 1]: Is that correct?
[SPEAKER 2]: No, that's an old one.
[SPEAKER 2]: No.
[SPEAKER 2]: My new email, I've had years, is the.omnizoa at gmail.
[SPEAKER 2]: T-H-E dot O-M-N-I-Z-O-A at gmail.com.
[SPEAKER 1]: Okay, got that, Mr. David.
[SPEAKER 1]: I'll be sending an email under my name, which is Alexis Stewart.
[SPEAKER 1]: And yeah, is it okay with you if I give you a call back maybe after working hours just to check if you were able to receive my email?
[SPEAKER 2]: Sure.
[SPEAKER 1]: Okay.
[SPEAKER 1]: All right.
[SPEAKER 1]: Thank you so much, Mr. David.
[SPEAKER 1]: This is Alexis again.
[SPEAKER 1]: Have a great day on your work and keep safe, okay?
[SPEAKER 2]: You too.
[SPEAKER 2]: Bye.
[SPEAKER 1]: Okay, bye.