This call is now being recorded.
My name is Movers, this is Gina.
How can I help you?
Hi Gina, I need help moving.
I'm being relocated to Chicago for a new job.
Okay, sure, we can definitely help you.
May I have your name?
It's Bob Davis, D-A-V-I-S.
Okay, I have Bob, D-O-B, Davis, D-A-V-I-S.
Yes.
Okay, and are you currently located in the Philadelphia area or are you near one of our national locations?
I'm in Philadelphia.
Okay, and what type of truck are you looking for to have for the move?
Largest one you got.
All right, no problem, Bob.
Where did you say you were relocating to again?
Was it Chicago?
Correct.
All right, and what date are you looking to move?
September 28th.
Okay, perfect, we're available on September 28th.
We'll take it.
Great, the large furniture trucks come with two movers.
You must rent the truck for a minimum of two days due to the distance.
Okay.
All right, I approximated the distance between Philadelphia and Chicago.
The price will be $1,065 per day and you must also pay tolls.
Okay, great.
How do I pay for that?
Okay, many of our customers put down $6,000 per day.
Okay, and how much is the total cost?
Okay, $1,000 per day.
Okay, how do I pay for that?
Okay, many of our customers put down 50% of the estimated price as a deposit.
Once arriving at your destination, an exact price will be reached and the difference will be due.
Most customers write out a check at that point.
Perfect.
Can I stop by the office this week to drop off the deposit?
Absolutely, I'm going to reserve that largest truck that we have for September 28th and 29th.
Is this correct?
Yes.
All right, I just want to confirm your name again.
It's Bob Davis.
Yes.
All right, and what is the address where we will be picking up the furniture?
It's 800 North Henderson Road in King of Prussia.
Okay, I have 800 North Henderson Road in King of Prussia.
Yes.
All right, Bob, we will see you in about a month.
Excellent, thank you.
Thank you.
Have a nice day.
You too.
Bye-bye.