[SPEAKER 2]: This call is now being recorded.
[SPEAKER 1]: My name is Movers, this is Gina.
[SPEAKER 1]: How can I help you?
[SPEAKER 2]: Hi Gina, I need help moving.
[SPEAKER 2]: I'm being relocated to Chicago for a new job.
[SPEAKER 1]: Okay, sure, we can definitely help you.
[SPEAKER 1]: May I have your name?
[SPEAKER 2]: It's Bob Davis, D-A-V-I-S.
[SPEAKER 1]: Okay, I have Bob, D-O-B, Davis, D-A-V-I-S.
[SPEAKER 2]: Yes.
[SPEAKER 1]: Okay, and are you currently located in the Philadelphia area or are you near one of our national locations?
[SPEAKER 2]: I'm in Philadelphia.
[SPEAKER 1]: Okay, and what type of truck are you looking for to have for the move?
[SPEAKER 2]: Largest one you got.
[SPEAKER 1]: All right, no problem, Bob.
[SPEAKER 1]: Where did you say you were relocating to again?
[SPEAKER 1]: Was it Chicago?
[SPEAKER 2]: Correct.
[SPEAKER 1]: All right, and what date are you looking to move?
[SPEAKER 2]: September 28th.
[SPEAKER 1]: Okay, perfect, we're available on September 28th.
[SPEAKER 2]: We'll take it.
[SPEAKER 1]: Great, the large furniture trucks come with two movers.
[SPEAKER 1]: You must rent the truck for a minimum of two days due to the distance.
[SPEAKER 2]: Okay.
[SPEAKER 1]: All right, I approximated the distance between Philadelphia and Chicago.
[SPEAKER 1]: The price will be $1,065 per day and you must also pay tolls.
[SPEAKER 2]: Okay, great.
[SPEAKER 2]: How do I pay for that?
[SPEAKER 2]: Okay, many of our customers put down $6,000 per day.
[SPEAKER 2]: Okay, and how much is the total cost?
[SPEAKER 2]: Okay, $1,000 per day.
[SPEAKER 2]: Okay, how do I pay for that?
[SPEAKER 1]: Okay, many of our customers put down 50% of the estimated price as a deposit.
[SPEAKER 1]: Once arriving at your destination, an exact price will be reached and the difference will be due.
[SPEAKER 1]: Most customers write out a check at that point.
[SPEAKER 2]: Perfect.
[SPEAKER 2]: Can I stop by the office this week to drop off the deposit?
[SPEAKER 1]: Absolutely, I'm going to reserve that largest truck that we have for September 28th and 29th.
[SPEAKER 1]: Is this correct?
[SPEAKER 2]: Yes.
[SPEAKER 1]: All right, I just want to confirm your name again.
[SPEAKER 1]: It's Bob Davis.
[SPEAKER 1]: Yes.
[SPEAKER 1]: All right, and what is the address where we will be picking up the furniture?
[SPEAKER 2]: It's 800 North Henderson Road in King of Prussia.
[SPEAKER 1]: Okay, I have 800 North Henderson Road in King of Prussia.
[SPEAKER 2]: Yes.
[SPEAKER 1]: All right, Bob, we will see you in about a month.
[SPEAKER 1]: Excellent, thank you.
[SPEAKER 1]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER 1]: Have a nice day.
[SPEAKER 2]: You too.
[SPEAKER 2]: Bye-bye.